buypoe.com 2010-03-17

# Privacy, Copyrights and Trademarks

> **Introduction**  
>  This is the privacy policy of BuyPoe.com and any companies within our group (referred to collectively as "BuyPoe"). It applies to all of our websites / services (referred to collectively as "our websites") on which it appears. 
> 
> We are committed to protecting your privacy and take special measures to ensure the confidentiality of personally identifiable information collected from or about you. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store and use such personally identifiable information. ("Personally identifiable information" is information that identifies you and can be used to contact or locate you in real life, such as your real full name, e-mail address, mobile telephone number, postal address or credit card information.) 
> 
> Please read this policy carefully. Your accepting it in full is a condition of your use of our websites (whether or not you are a subscriber). If you do not agree with this policy, or any part, please do not use our websites. Your using any of our websites is treated as an acceptance of the version of this policy in effect at the time of your use. 
> 
> We may change this policy at any time. Please check it whenever you return to the site. We will treat your continued use of our websites as acceptance of these changes from their effective date as shown above. 
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us by emailing [dave@buypoe.com](mailto:dave@buypoe.com) and do not use our websites until you are satisfied and can accept this policy in its entirety. 
> 
> **What personally identifiable information do we collect and store?**  
>  No personally identifiable information is collected when you merely access the public areas of our websites or when you play our single player games.   
>  We collect and store information which you voluntarily provide via forms or otherwise on our websites, electronic or other communications with us. You may opt-out of providing any such information by simply choosing not to complete the form requesting the information, and hence choosing not to use that particular service. 
> 
> **What other information is collected and stored?**  
>  We use cookies, collect and store IP-addresses, alphanumeric IDs and other unique identifiers in order to identify specific computers that access our websites. We identify and store the versions of Java and .NET (if any) on your computer along with your browser and operating system.   
>  We generate and store logs indicating usage of our websites such as activity in our games and public and private chat communications. This includes monitoring play patterns and anti-tamper checks which verify the correct internal operation of our software and are designed to spot abusive or inappropriate activities.   
>  We may track your use of certain features and areas of our websites to help us improve them.   
>  If our client software held on your computer fails, it sends an automatic error report to our server to help us fix it. This error report only includes information about the internal state of our own client software and which browser/java version it is running on. It does not include data from elsewhere on your system and so does not reveal personally identifiable information to us. 
> 
> **What happens to the information provided/collected?**  
>  The information we collect may be used:   
>  a) To process your payment for membership subscriptions or other goods or services ordered on our site or to fulfil such orders. 
> 
> b) To provide our customer support service, and to verify any claims or requests you make if you use our customer support service. 
> 
> c) To enforce our [terms and conditions](http://buypoe.com/showthread.php?t=96), and prevent or detect 
> 
> hacking activities, security breaches or safety risks in connection with our websites. 
> 
> d) To send service announcements and messages (for example, a reminder sent to the members' Message Centre if a subscription payment is due or if member credit has expired). 
> 
> e) To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our websites. We may share this anonymous information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
> 
> f) For our own internal marketing and demographic studies and to help us improve our websites. 
> 
> g) In the event of an actual or proposed (including as part of negotiations for any) merger, or business combination or sale of substantially all of our assets or a business operation to which such information relates, or as provided under bankruptcy or applicable insolvency laws or by the enforcement of equitable rights. 
> 
> h) To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government, regulatory or law enforcement authority, to protect or assist in protecting our users, systems or the public, or to otherwise enforce legal rights as determined in our sole and absolute discretion. 
> 
> i) If you have agreed on our websites, to send you email newsletters about our games, including new game features and special offers. 
> 
> j) As set out elsewhere in our privacy policy.
> 
> We care about protecting your privacy, and with the exception of the uses specified above, we will not sell, transfer, rent out, share or disclose your personally identifiable information to other companies. 
> 
> **Cookies**  
>  A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.   
>  Session cookies are temporary, and remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site. We use session cookies to enable us to authenticate users during game sessions.   
>  Persistent cookies remain in the cookie file of your browser for a specific period. Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.   
>  We use persistent cookies to track your country (to enable us to provide country-specific content) and to track whether you entered our websites from a link on site of one of our business partners. Persistent cookies also allow you to login when you return to our site, by storing your login information on your own computer. Additionally we may use persistent cookies to store information about which adverts from our site have been displayed to you to help avoid showing the same one repeatedly or to provide information that we hope will meet your needs or interests.   
>  Our advertisers and technology partners also use cookies and other similar technologies. For more information about this, see under "Third Parties" below. 
> 
> **Safeguarding your personally identifiable information  
>  **We will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent we believe it reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and will protect it using the same level of safeguards we use to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of our own equivalent proprietary information. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer any personally identifiable information in accordance with this policy will agree to provide sufficient protection. We may store or transfer personal information outside the European Economic Area for the purposes stated in this policy. Note that while we strive to protect all our personally identifiable information, we have all heard of data breaches in well-respected financial and governmental institutions and we cannot ever fully guarantee that such breaches will not happen. We will inform you of any material data breaches that we discover that may compromise your personally identifiable information. 
> 
> **Review, correction and deletion of information from our records**  
>  If for data protection purposes you are concerned that the personally identifiable information which we hold about you is not accurate, or should you wish to have your personal information removed from our records.
> 
> Game Copyrights and Trademarks
> 
> Battle.net®  
>  ©1996 - 2002 Blizzard Entertainment. All rights reserved. Battle.net and Blizzard Entertainment are trademarks or registered trademarks of Blizzard Entertainment in the U.S. and/or other countries.
> 
> Blizzard Entertainment®  
>  Blizzard Entertainment is a trademark or registered trademark of Blizzard Entertainment in the U.S. and/or other countries. All rights reserved. 
> 
> Diablo®  
>  ©1996 Blizzard Entertainment. All rights reserved. Diablo and Blizzard Entertainment are trademarks or registered trademarks of Blizzard Entertainment in the U.S. and/or other countries. 
> 
> Diablo® II  
>  ©2000 Blizzard Entertainment. All rights reserved. Diablo and Blizzard Entertainment are trademarks or registered trademarks of Blizzard Entertainment in the U.S. and/or other countries. 
> 
> Diablo® II: Lord of Destruction™  
>  ©2001 Blizzard Entertainment. All rights reserved. Lord of Destruction is a trademark and Diablo and Blizzard Entertainment are trademarks or registered trademarks of Blizzard Entertainment in the U.S. and/or other countries.
> 
> Puzzle Pirates™   
>  © 2001-2009 Three Rings Design, Inc. All Rights Reserved. 
> 
> World of Warcraft™   
>  ©2009 Blizzard Entertainment, Inc. All rights reserved.
> 
> Runescape™  
>  copyright © 1999 - 2009 Jagex Ltd.
> 
> Habbo™  
>  © 2008 - 2009 Sulake Corporation Oy. HABBO is a registered trademark of Sulake Corporation Oy. American Idol™ 19 TV Ltd & FremantleMedia North America, Inc. Licensed by FremantleMedia Enterprises. All rights reserved by their respective right holders.
